{"task_id": "HumanEval/10", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is '', what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    if not string:\n        return ''\n\n    beginning_of_suffix = 0\n\n    while not is_palindrome(string[beginning_of_suffix:]):\n        beginning_of_suffix += 1\n\n    return string + string[:beginning_of_suffix][::-1]\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]''[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/114", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is [2, 3, 4, 1, 2, 4], what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    max_sum = 0\n    s = 0\n    for num in nums:\n        s += -num\n        if (s < 0):\n            s = 0\n        max_sum = max(s, max_sum)\n    if max_sum == 0:\n        max_sum = max(-i for i in nums)\n    min_sum = -max_sum\n    return min_sum\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]1, \"This prints if this assert fails 1 (good for debugging!)\"[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/23", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is '', what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    return len(string)\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]0[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/28", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is [], what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    return ''.join(strings)\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]''[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/131", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is 5, what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    product = 1\n    odd_count = 0\n    for digit in str(n):\n        int_digit = int(digit)\n        if int_digit%2 == 1:\n            product= product*int_digit\n            odd_count+=1\n    if odd_count ==0:\n        return 0\n    else:\n        return product\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]5[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/88", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is [], what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    return [] if len(array) == 0 else sorted(array, reverse= (array[0]+array[-1]) % 2 == 0) \n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output][], \"Error\"[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/110", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is [1, 2, 3, 4], [1, 2, 3, 4], what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    odd = 0\n    even = 0\n    for i in lst1:\n        if i%2 == 1:\n            odd += 1\n    for i in lst2:\n        if i%2 == 0:\n            even += 1\n    if even >= odd:\n        return \"YES\"\n    return \"NO\"\n            \n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]\"YES\"[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/34", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is [5, 3, 5, 2, 3, 3, 9, 0, 123], what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    return sorted(list(set(l)))\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output][0, 2, 3, 5, 9, 123][/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/62", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is [3, 1, 2, 4, 5], what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    return [(i * x) for i, x in enumerate(xs)][1:]\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output][1, 4, 12, 20][/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/70", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is [1, 2, 3, 4], what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    res, switch = [], True\n    while lst:\n        res.append(min(lst) if switch else max(lst))\n        lst.remove(res[-1])\n        switch = not switch\n    return res\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output][1, 4, 2, 3][/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/115", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is [[0,0,1,0], [0,1,0,0], [1,1,1,1]], 1, what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    return sum([math.ceil(sum(arr)/capacity) for arr in grid])\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]6, \"Error\"[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/0", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is [1.0, 2.0, 3.9, 4.0, 5.0, 2.2], 0.3, what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    for idx, elem in enumerate(numbers):\n        for idx2, elem2 in enumerate(numbers):\n            if idx != idx2:\n                distance = abs(elem - elem2)\n                if distance < threshold:\n                    return True\n\n    return False\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]True[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/56", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is None, what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    depth = 0\n    for b in brackets:\n        if b == \"<\":\n            depth += 1\n        else:\n            depth -= 1\n        if depth < 0:\n            return False\n    return depth == 0\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]None[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/118", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is \"yogurt\", what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    if len(word) < 3:\n        return \"\"\n\n    vowels = {\"a\", \"e\", \"i\", \"o\", \"u\", \"A\", \"E\", 'O', 'U', 'I'}\n    for i in range(len(word)-2, 0, -1):\n        if word[i] in vowels:\n            if (word[i+1] not in vowels) and (word[i-1] not in vowels):\n                return word[i]\n    return \"\"\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]\"u\"[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/87", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is [], 1, what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    coords = [(i, j) for i in range(len(lst)) for j in range(len(lst[i])) if lst[i][j] == x]\n    return sorted(sorted(coords, key=lambda x: x[1], reverse=True), key=lambda x: x[0])\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output][][/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/75", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is 5, what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    def is_prime(n):\n        for j in range(2,n):\n            if n%j == 0:\n                return False\n        return True\n\n    for i in range(2,101):\n        if not is_prime(i): continue\n        for j in range(2,101):\n            if not is_prime(j): continue\n            for k in range(2,101):\n                if not is_prime(k): continue\n                if i*j*k == a: return True\n    return False\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]False[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/55", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is 10, what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    if n == 0:\n        return 0\n    if n == 1:\n        return 1\n    return fib(n - 1) + fib(n - 2)\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]55[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/52", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is None, what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    for e in l:\n        if e >= t:\n            return False\n    return True\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]None[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/157", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is 3, 4, 5, what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    return a*a == b*b + c*c or b*b == a*a + c*c or c*c == a*a + b*b\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]True, \"This prints if this assert fails 1 (good for debugging!)\"[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
{"task_id": "HumanEval/79", "prompt": "You are an AI programming assistant, utilizing the DeepSeek Coder model, developed by DeepSeek Company, and you only answer questions related to computer science. For politically sensitive questions, security and privacy issues, and other non-computer science questions, you will refuse to answer.\n### Instruction:\nIf the string is 0, what will the following code return?\nThe return value prediction must be enclosed between [Output] and [/Output] tags. For example : [Output]prediction[/Output].\n\n    return \"db\" + bin(decimal)[2:] + \"db\"\n\n\n### Response:\n", "expect": "[Output]\"db0db\"[/Output]", "is_correct": null}
